(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
EIYAA 【お弁当】 差し入れ参加者様
EIYAA [Bento] Gift Participants
うまくいかない今日だって即寝るだ
Even if today doesn't go well, I'll sleep immediately.
明日の教科書水に落としたら
If I drop tomorrow's textbook in water...
何だってやれそうだ
...I feel like I can do anything.
落書きの中光った思いを
The feelings that shone inside the doodle...
君とこうして交わし合えたなんて
...that I could exchange with you like this...
嘘みたいだな
...it feels like a lie.
もっと瞬いて記して
Twinkle more and mark this moment.
だんだんと増えた輪の中
Inside the circle that gradually increased...
理不尽
...unreasonableness...
考えず
...without thinking...
単純なまま行こう
...let's go on simply.
楽しかった日々ほら一瞬でしょ
Fun days are just a moment, you see?
昨日よりも加速してる
Accelerating more than yesterday.
ちゃんと繋いで手
Hold hands properly.
簡単じゃないホームの掛け声は
The cheers of 'home' aren't simple.
いつも君が明るく放って
You always release them brightly...
支えてくれる
...and support me.
ずっと刻まれて光るよ
It will be engraved and shine forever.
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
そらちゃん！そらちゃん！
Sora-chan! Sora-chan!
2025.10.2 Thu
8th Anniversary Party Starry Bl∞min'
with DJ ANKIMO
TOKINO SORA
2020 2nd year
2021 3rd year
2022 4th year
2023 5th year
2024 6th year
Ten! Nine! Eight! Seven! Six! Five! Four! Three! Two! One! Zero!
行くよ！
Here we go!
最初の合図なっちゃって
The first signal has sounded,
世界線を突破しちゃって
breaking right through the world line.
しっぽ仕掛けのときめきを
A tail-powered excitement...
ニャン！
Meow!
16bitの風
A 16-bit wind,
聞こえてきて　なんじゃこりゃ
I hear it coming, what on earth is this?
動き出す平成
The Heisei era starts to move,
すれ違い揺らぐ
wavering as we pass by.
もう一回
One more time,
まだ冷めない
not cooling down yet,
ノンストップで
nonstop,
この指にとまれ
gather round this finger.
追加コンティニュー招待
An invitation via extra continue.
まだ足りない
Still not enough,
SOSのサイン
an SOS sign.
もういいかい
Are you ready yet?
もう待てない
I can't wait anymore!
いますぐアクセス全開
Full access right now,
連投させてメッセージ
let me spam these messages.
最初の合図なっちゃって
The first signal has sounded,
世界線を突破しちゃって
breaking right through the world line.
君の音が聞きたいんだ
I want to hear your sound.
意識が痺れちゃって
My senses are going numb,
奇跡を灯しちゃって
lighting up a miracle.
行き着いたらそこは
When we arrive there,
無限大よ
it's infinity!
共鳴感情
Resonant emotion,
その声を聞かせてよ
let me hear that voice.
夢進行形
Dream in progress,
理屈を超えて
transcending logic.
目覚めたこの感情
This awakened emotion,
アナログに変換して
convert it to analog.
ひとひらの
A single flake,
最高の
the best one.
止められないこの衝動
This unstoppable impulse...
止まんない！
won't stop!
私待ってるよ
I'm waiting,
待ってるよ
waiting,
I'm waiting.
空っぽのキャンバスに
On this empty canvas,
あなたはまだ色を
you still haven't put any color.
一歩踏み出して
Take one step forward,
ここから始まるストーリー
the story begins from here.
夢で見た景色は
The scenery I saw in my dreams
憧れのままで
remains just a longing.
終わらないで
Don't let it end.
私待ってるよ
I'm waiting,
待ってるよ
waiting,
この広い空で
in this vast sky.
あの日から君がここへ
Since that day, for you to reach here...
たどり着くのを
to arrive here.
今歌ってるよ
I'm singing now,
歌ってるよ
singing,
夢の方目掛けて
aiming towards the dream.
きっとどうか届いて
Surely, please reach it!
届いて！
Reach it!
描いた地図は広がって
The map I drew expands,
まだ続く明日へ
towards the tomorrow that continues.
夢みたいな色で
With dream-like colors,
まだ追いかけ続けて
keep chasing them.
チャレンジは止まらない
The challenge doesn't stop.
点と点を繋げて
Connecting the dots,
私待ってるよ
I'm waiting,
待ってるよ
waiting,
今もずっとここで
still right here, forever.
いつの日か君が
Someday, I hope you...
見つけてくれるように
will find me.
ねえ 待ってるよ
Hey, I'm waiting,
待ってるよ
waiting,
時空を超えて
transcending space-time.
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting,
時が変わっても
Even if the times change,
同じ星が奏でた向こうへと
To the beyond played by the same stars,
飛び立ったとしても
Even if we fly away.
寂しくても 何度でも
Even if it's lonely, again and again,
歓声を原動力に変えて
Turning your cheers into my driving force.
ここまで歩んできた私なら
If it's me who has walked this far,
私 持ってるよ 持ってるよ 持ってるよ
I have it, I have it, I really have it.
この日の行く末
The destiny of this day,
あの日から君が
Since that day, you...
見つけてくれた
...found me.
意味を知ってるよ 知ってるよ 知ってるよ
I know the meaning, I know, I know.
目指した場所で
At the place we aimed for,
いいことあるさ
Good things will happen.
届いてる 届いてる 届いてる
It's reaching you, reaching you, reaching you.
夢を叶えて この空へ
Making dreams come true, to this sky.
みんな、この曲待ってたでしょ？
Everyone, you were waiting for this song, right?
しっかり掛け声、覚えてきたよね？
You remembered the calls properly, didn't you?
一緒にフーフー言って、盛り上がっちゃえよー！
Let's say Fu-Fu- together and get hyped!
せーの！
Ready, set!
我らの宇宙の始まりは (パパヤ)
Our universe's beginning is (Papaya)
触れた瞬間 アララララ (パパヤ)
The moment we touched, arararara (Papaya)
ああ これは困った
Ah, this is a problem.
二度と元に戻らない 大！爆！発！
Never returning to normal, Big! Explo! Sion!
そして星が生まれまして (パパヤ)
And then a star was born (Papaya)
明け方の一番星は (パパヤ)
The first star at dawn is (Papaya)
ああ あなたと出会った
Ah, I met you.
これは次元を揺るがす 大！発！見！
This is a dimension-shaking Big! Dis! Covery!
このままハート打ち上げて どこまでも高い宇宙まで
Launching my heart like this, to the endlessly high universe.
めっちゃ飛んじゃいたいっ！
I want to fly so much!
さあ スタースタースタート切ったこのラブは
Now, this love that has Star Star Started,
あなたがいなきゃ待ったなしで 超！新！星！
Without you, it's a Super! Nova! with no waiting!
するぞ？ (オー・オ・オー！)
I'll do it? (Oh oh oh!)
しちゃうぞ！？ (オー・オ・オー！)
I'm gonna do it!? (Oh oh oh!)
あなたに言ってますっ！
I'm talking to you!
ドュユアンダ スタ、スタ、スタンド
Do you under-sta-sta-stand,
あの、わかってる？
Um, do you understand?
ほら目の前にずっとある 一！等！星！
Look, the First! Magnitude! Star! that's always right here!
みてる？ (オー・オ・オー！)
Watching? (Oh oh oh!)
きーてる！？ (オー・オ・オー！)
Listening!? (Oh oh oh!)
そのビッグバン気づいて！！！！！！
Notice that Big Bang!!!!!!
愛は地球くらいに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ
Love has expanded to the size of the Earth and become like this!
そうさ第三の惑星は
That's right, the third planet is...
このときのためのスター！
...a star for this moment!
デデデ電波を送信
Sending de-de-de-radio waves,
あなたのハートにノーティス
Notice to your heart.
「暇なときでいいよ？」みたいなカオして
Making a face like 'Whenever you're free is fine?'
めっちゃめちゃ待機……！
Waiting super duper...!
チョットの反応くれたら喜ばしい
It'd be delightful if you gave a little reaction,
てか、こんなの逃すなんて嘆かわしい…
I mean, missing this is deplorable...
いやぁ～、これはスゴいな！
Wow, this is amazing!
つまりあなたとわたしの創！世！記！
In other words, it's our Gen! E! Sis!
このままハートあなたごと連れて彼方を目指したら
If I take my heart and you along to aim for the beyond,
めっちゃ飛んじゃったっ！
We flew so much!
あぁ、スタースタースタートしたこのラブは
Ah, this love that has Star Star Started,
あなたがいなきゃいまごろ超新星
Without you, it would be a supernova by now.
してた…… (オー・オ・オー！)
It would have... (Oh oh oh!)
してたが！ (オー・オ・オー！)
It would have, but! (Oh oh oh!)
ほら、今日まで続いた――！
Look, it lasted until today!
ドュユアンダ スタ、スタ、スタンド
Do you under-sta-sta-stand,
ちゃんと、わかってね！？
Understand properly, okay!?
いっそう光度まして輝く 一！等！星！
Shining even brighter, First! Magnitude! Star!
あなたと！ (オー・オ・オー！)
With you! (Oh oh oh!)
わたしで！ (オー・オ・オー！)
And me! (Oh oh oh!)
ビッグバンしたいの！！！！！！
I want to Big Bang!!!!!!
みんなー！見えてるー？聞こえてるー？
Everyone! Can you see me? Can you hear me?
今日も2日目、そらパ2025ですよ！
It's the second day today too, SoraPa 2025!
みんな、今さっき言っちゃった…
Everyone, I just said it earlier...
見えてる？聞こえてる？
Can you see me? Can you hear me?
可愛い、ありがとう。
Cute, thank you.
オレンジジュース美味しいよ。
Orange juice is delicious.
昨日もやりましたが、今日もね、
We did this yesterday, but today too,
あの掛け声、みんなでやっていきましょうね。
let's do that call-and-response together, okay?
やぁーというわけで、はぁ、1年半ぶりなんですよ。
So, *sigh*, it's been a year and a half.
まぁ昨日ぶりだから、
Well, since I saw you yesterday,
まぁ1日ぶりですね。ふふふ。
it's actually been one day. Hehehe.
まぁ今日も2日目だよって人！
Well, who is attending for the second day today!
今日が初めてだよって人！
Who is here for the first time today!
そもそもライブ自体初めてですよって人！
Who is attending a live concert for the first time ever!
おー！じゃあ、ライブデビューですね。ありがとうございます。
Ooh! So it's your live debut. Thank you very much.
では、全員に声出してもらいたいな。
Well then, I want everyone to raise their voice.
とりあえず…全員！！
For now... EVERYONE!!
声出せるかな？
Can you shout?
出せなかったらまぁ手で振るだけでもいいよね。
If you can't, just waving your hands is fine too.
女の子！！
Girls!!
男の子！！
Boys!!
最前席！！
Front row seats!!
海外のみんな！
Everyone from overseas!
コメント！
Comments!
今「YAY」って言ってくれてる。「YAY」って言ってくれてる。
They're saying 'YAY' right now. Saying 'YAY'.
そして、左のみんな！
And, everyone on the left!
右のみんな！
Everyone on the right!
全員！！
EVERYONE!!
よし、最高じゃないですか。
Alright, isn't that the best?
みんな、声枯らす準備できてるって感じ？
Everyone ready to shout until you lose your voice?
いい、見えてる見えてる。
Good, I can see you, I can see you.
前の方、後ろの方。
The front area, the back area.
前の方、後ろの方…
The front area, the back area...
どこ見てんだろうね。
Where am I looking, I wonder.
はい、というわけでね。あ、ありがとうありがとうありがとう。
Okay, so. Ah, thank you, thank you, thank you.
いやみんなのね、応援も…
Man, everyone's support...
今日なんかザリT率高いね。
Today the 'Zari-T' rate is high, huh.
めちゃくちゃ青い。なんか世界が青い。
It's super blue. Like the world is blue.
ザリTじゃないのか。
Is it not the Zari-T?
もしかしてあれかな？
Could it be that?
今回のライブのTシャツの人もいる？
Are there people wearing this concert's T-shirt too?
あ、やっぱそうだよね。Tシャツも青だもんね。
Ah, I knew it. The T-shirt is blue too, isn't it.
すごい、ありがとうございます。もうね、みんなが外で写真撮って…
Amazing, thank you very much. I saw everyone taking photos outside...
「来た！今から…待ちきれない！」ってやってるの、
going 'I'm here! Starting now... I can't wait!'...
すごい見てましたから。ありがとうございます。
I was really watching that. Thank you very much.
とね、こうやって喋ってるんですが、YouTubeをご覧の皆さん！
So, I'm talking like this, but, everyone watching on YouTube!
なんと…まだ来たばっかりなんだけど…
Surprisingly... I just got here, but...
まぁ本当に3曲しかやってないからまだ来たばっかりかもしれない。
well, I've really only done 3 songs so I might have just got here.
いや、物足りないなぁと思う人、ぜひね、なんかどっか…
Well, those who think it's not enough, please, somewhere...
ここここここここ…どっかに概要欄があるので、
here here here here... there's a description box somewhere,
そこから、配信チケットとか買って続きを見てもらえると、
so from there, if you buy a ticket and watch the rest,
わたくし、は、噛んだ。
I... ha, I stumbled.
とっても嬉しいなと思います。
I think I would be very happy.
ありがとう。というわけで、早速ね、
Thank you. So, moving right along,
お喋りばっかしてたらただの雑談枠になっちゃうのでね。
if we just chat, it'll just become a casual talk stream.
次の曲にも行って…いこうと思うんですが。
I think I'll go... move on to the next song.
まぁね、昨日歌ってなくて待ってた曲あるんじゃない？
Well, isn't there a song I didn't sing yesterday you've been waiting for?
次の曲は…イェーイ！新アルバムから！
The next song is... Yaaay! From the new album!
ダンサブルな！ダンスダンスダンスな曲を歌ってみようと思います！
A danceable! I think I'll sing a dance, dance, dance song!
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
Reached out my hand to the mirage
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。 ★ライブチケット購入はコチラ ▶▶ SPWN
The free introductory broadcast ends here. ★Purchase Live Tickets Here ▶▶ SPWN
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The free opening broadcast ends here.
ライブチケット購入はコチラ >> SPWN
Purchase live tickets here >> SPWN